ided by holy
Thank you.
All of the air, it seems to
be flowing over to Wamuu.
My ultimate mastery, atmospheric rift!
That's only wind!
I know you're near the flame.
I sense it, though I can't
see exactly where that is.
But I am going to find you eventually.
Now that I've prevented you from
gathering your Hormone energy,
I'm going to cut you in half!
Atmospheric Rift is Wamuu's
supreme final weapon.
The pipes he uses to
cloak himself take in huge
amounts of air and then
unbelievably compress it.
The air is then blasted from
an orifice thinner than paper.
It is a razor made of wind.
But it creates heat and friction
at levels terrible even for Wamuu.
His body cannot handle it.
He is falling apart.
But he is certainly a breathtaking
figure, tragic and heroic.
Victory is yours, Wamuu.
Take his life as a bomb
for your wound. Shoujo!
It's getting close!
Time to pull off one of
my famous tricks now!
This one's called the Harmon Oil Trick!
His lungs are literally
high-pressure oxygen tanks!
Those pipes, if I can only hit
them, he'd inhale the flaming oil?
which in turn would create
an internal explosion!
But this is the very
last ace up my sleeve!
If I mess it up...
Got you now!
Your life is mine damn it.
That's your choice fool!
I can sense anything that is
far enough away from the fire.
You're out of tricks and that cry
of yours gave away your position.
Atmospheric rift.
SIR!
Lend me your strays!
Another fire attack!
I told you I can sense these things.
And now I will cut you in
half to claim my victory!
Jojo, no!
Now he has finally won.
Wamu, let me tell you
exactly when you lost.
It was when I threw Caesar's scarf. Huh?
Don't you get it?
I meant for you to cut the
bottle in half the entire time.
Your ability to do it so quickly and
easily is what led to your downfall.
The oil inside of it is now vaporizing.
And look, you see the bandana?
All the pieces flying around?
Every little fragment is still on
fire, and they're entering my body.
Wamuu, you have been a
worthy and admirable fighter.
But a powerful ally named Caesar
was with me throughout this contest.
He was defeated.
Lord Wamuu, how could he have lost?
Jojo, be careful, he can regenerate,
even like that after being blown to bits.
You have to use your strongest
hormone to destroy him completely.
So it is finally over now, Jojo.
It is.
You took revenge for Caesar.
Yes, I did.
Then go ahead.
Finish it.
I will!
Oh.
What is going on?
That smoke isn't from the flaming oil.
It's coming from your wounds.
The hormone from your
arms spread through you.
Every part of you is infected now.
You are dissolving.
I can only imagine the agony you feel.
I can't prevent you from dying now.
But there's this.
My blood can at least ease your pain.
Why do you want to shame me?
I have made peace with myself. Stop!
I don't need pity from you!
Is that what you think?
That this is done out of pity for you? No.
Why didn't you destroy Caesar's bubble of
blood that carried his bandana and ring,
knowing full well that they
posed a serious threat to you?
Was that pity?
It was because the man was
a worthy and noble warrior.
He deserved to be honored for that.
What you'll say next is,
Jojo, you can't mean...
Yes, I do, Wamu.
The honor you showed my friend, Caesar's
warrior spirit, had earned your respect.
So in return, I wanted to find a
way to honor your warrior spirit.
My blood is a tribute to you.
You beat me, Jojo.
And as a warrior, it would now appear
that you stand taller than I do.
EA, kill the bastard!
Hold!
What betrayal is this?
Huh?
You cowardly animals!
Wamuu!
Why do that?
I am Wamuu.
Although sworn to Lord Kars, I will
not allow the vampires to attack you.
It's not because of sentiment.
I told Caesar this as well.
To me, only the strong truly existed.
Victory was the single
quality to be admired.
I existed only according
to my own code of honor.
Jojo, please understand.
To me, immortality was something
utterly unimportant and trivial.
All that has ever mattered to
me was living up to my code.
And now, I desire that you
should drink the antidote.
You must do it before I
dissolve completely away.
You won't see it though.
I don't need eyes, words, or a horn.
I will know it.
What matters is that you do it.
I have no regrets.
I am glad I was able to witness
your growth as a warrior.
Perhaps the reason I
lived these thousands of
years was so that I could
meet you at the end.
Farewell to you, Warrior Jojo.
Wamu became one with the wind.
Jojo gave his opponent one final salute.
Though no tears fell, they
had shared a silent song.
They had shared a warrior's affinity.
Wamu, you must kill him.
But, my lord Kars, with utmost respect,
he is only an innocent young boy.
That's true, just a boy.
That is the reason he must die.
If these Hormone users
are allowed to live,
they're likely to become
our mortal enemies.
And humans grow very quickly indeed.
Hmm.
Is it beyond you?
It would seem I must
demonstrate how it is done.
Now, in resolving the problem...
is handled like this, Wamuu.
Wamuu.
He was too pure in his warrior philosophy.
And he became weak as a result.
Well, that's the end of Wamuu.
Indeed it is.
What a disappointment. You're right.
He's only a poser.
Your followers are such base creatures.
Makes me want to vomit.
No, don't!
Don't curse me!
I alone am the only one to remain,
because this world and
all in it belong to me.
Look at him, look!
Lord Kars is amazing!
Our lord is ready to fight!
Listen,
Lord Kars, there's no reason for you to
waste time on any one-on-one battles.
Forget the rules.
Let us kill these two for you.
Or you lord will turn
them into spades of blood!
Just what I thought you would do.
I told you.
The redstone! Look!
It's me against Kars, one-on-one.
But if those terms aren't to your liking,
why don't I just smash this
thing right here and now?
I will honor my word.
A one-on-one fight. Count on it.
My promise stands.
That is why I chose to
reveal my horn to you.
As for my underlings' behavior, as you
can clearly see, they are already dead.
My Lord Coors!
All I want is that red stone.
However, though, ACDC and Wamuu
were my comrades for 10,000 years.
I have no choice but to honor both their
warrior deaths and their warrior pride.
I will fight you Hamon users fairly,
and then I will finish
this with my own two hands.
For you, Lisa Lisa,
seeing the fighter you are, I will
not think of you as merely a woman.
I will fight you with all the
strength I have at my command.
Come with me.
That is where we shall fight.
The Temple at Pies Bernina.
Champions of battle would come here to
drink the blood of those they had felled,
mixed with liquor.
They thanked the gods
for the gift of life.
It's not an arena, but it
will serve for our fight.
Coach Lisa Lisa, you may be extremely
skilled, but you are still a woman.
He doesn't look as strong as Wamu was.
Let me take him for you.
I will not.
I didn't live my life
as I did and train all
those years to be replaced by
some stripling. Oh, that's right.
You have lived a lot of years.
I shall use my brilliant bone blades.
It would offend Wamu's memory if I didn't
offer you the weapon of your choice.
Feel free to pick anything you like.
My scarf will be more than sufficient.
As you will.
And now, let's fight.
Remarkable.
There is no violence in his stance.
How can he fight without violence?
What's the matter?
Are you not ready?
Apparently, the first move is mine!
He disappeared completely
in that sudden white light.
Where'd he go?
Cause is here.
I can feel him.
But he seems to be coming
from above as well as below.
Attack of the brilliant Boneblade!
Look, in the pillar, there's a crack!
Snake Muffler!
Huh?
What you don't know is
this Satoporosia Beetle
Scarf is able to conduct
hormone energy perfectly.
It's both a deadly weapon
and a life detector.
And it protects against
being attacked from behind!
All right, a knockout!
My wonderful coach really got him good.
He didn't really compare to Wamuu,
but dogs who bark rarely bite.
Coach, I have to say that you
really are better than me.
Help me!
Help me, Lord Kars!
Oh, Kars is behind her!
Then who's that?
Who's at her feet?
It can't be!
What the hell is going on?
Kaz wasn't the one fighting
with her, he used a double!
Hmph, what stupidity.
Why would I ever choose
to fight one-on-one?
The only thing I wanted out
of this was the Red Stone,
because I planned to become
the ultimate life form.
I am not a warrior philosopher like
Wamuu was, nor am I a romantic.
No matter the method
utilized, in the end...
Victory is the only thing that matters!
So, that's why I sensed no violence.
He never had any intention of fighting me.
It's over!
Joe... Joe...
I have the red stone.
The only thing that's left is for all
of you to make me happy by killing Jojo!
CAUSE! CAUSE!
You are going to pay!
CAUSE!
Out of the way! Move back!
Customers took down stealth and kill you!
Zoom punch!
You're homo!
I don't think it's working anymore!
You're weak now, so
we're - Remove overdrive!
Jojo, you look completely worn out.
Your breathing is ragged.
Your Hamon level is weak.
And you're the only one left out of all
of the Hamon users that Lisa Lisa trained.
Can you last?
Will you last?
Jojo, think you can beat me?
He-he-he, hmmm.
What?
It can't be gone!
Let's rip off his skin!
Oh, crap! You can try!
That light!
And that face!
This is your warning, Vampires!
You are now facing Major von
Stroheim, unser German elite!
And we represent the special forces of
the Speedwagon Foundation! Jojo! Jojo!
Da!
Speedwagon, you look great!
And Smokey, too!
You're a sight for sore eyes!
My right leg might be stiff now, but my
body is better than it ever was before!
Now all your vampires will see
what German science can do!
HE'S A ULTRA VIOLENT BLOODLINE!
It was the Speedwagon Foundation
that made them small enough to carry.
But our boy does like to brag.
Hm...
Crafty creatures, no question.
Hm?
I don't see Jojo down there.
Gone again!
oh you're just as quick as ever aren't
you take eyes off you for a second
and there you are putting another
little scheme in play you crossed a line
no honor earns you no consideration
you said it would be a fair fight but
attacked Lisa Lisa in a cowardly ambush
thereby showing what you're made of.
And you have betrayed the honor
and memory of your friend, Wamu.
Save your indignation.
Your outrage means nothing.
Any action is a means to
an end for what I desire.
The thing that matters
to me is the Red Stone.
Battling over thousands of years means
minimizing danger, not taking any risk?
and moving your pawns
very carefully indeed.
This is what the battle has been about.
And to show you how good I am at this,
I'm going to maneuver you effortlessly
to your death. Listen to me!
For your information, Kars!
I've never hated anyone before
this day, but you I hate!
You really hate me?
Then show me, Jojo.
Let's go one-on-one.
We'll have that fair
fight you wanted to have.
Lisa Lisa is almost dead.
But not completely yet.
I left her alive.
My plan is to let her live for a while.
And why would I do that
she's just another pawn
a worthless little pawn
I Can use against you?
You utter bastard!
Now I've tied her feet
together with this rope.
And do you know why?
Why would I do such a thing as this?
This is why!
Lisa Lisa, no!
Off you go!
If she hits the ground, she'll be dead.
If you don't save her in a few seconds,
she'll be a Lisa-Lisa-shaped splatter!
What? Jojo!
Lisa-Lisa! Huh? Lisa-Lisa?
That Lisa-Lisa?
Do you mean to say she's the baby?
On the ship Granny Arena told us about?
Then that means she is JoJo's...
Now that you can't move from that spot,
here's how efficient battle can be, JoJo!
I'll very calmly walk right up to you and
slice you to pieces while you can't move!
Cars, you bastard!
There's a place waiting for you in hell!
Jojo doesn't know.
He doesn't know the woman he's
trying to save is his mother.
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
I'll spend the day your way.
Call it morning, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I'll spend the day your way.
Cold in morning, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
In and out around the lake.
Mountains come out of the sky.
And they'll stand there.
One mile over, we'll be there.
And we'll see you.
Ten, two summers, we'll be there.
Locking with you.
Twenty, four, five, five, let me see.
I'll be there with you.
Have you finished disposing
of those vampires yet?
I'm taking your life at
the moment of my choice.
The scarf is a gamble.
Poor little child.
Von Stroheim, you must stop!
This can't be!